

EWERTON BRAGA DE JESUS

UX & UI DESIGNER

Married - 28 years forewerton@gmail.com +55 11 94207-1936 linkedin.com/in/forewerton/

SUMMARY

Hello, my name is Ewerton and I am a UX/UI designer with about 8 years of experience designing, prototyping and developing websites and apps. Graduated in Publicity and Advertising and specializes in UI and Ux, I have focused my studies in the last two years on Ux Research and Strategy.

I am a passionate strategist and analyst who get concerned about what and how people think and use products daily, whether online or offline context.

Besides this, I also have a background as a front-end developer where I converting prototypes that I created on Adobe XD, Figma and Invision into pixel-perfect responsive websites, apps and softwares like ERP.

With knowledge and experience as an endeavor, SEO, Google Analytics and Adwords, I can resolve problems that involving more than simple screens, but real problems searching always the better alternative to reach the goals with what is possible with the current technology and stakeholders' interests.

I am in love with strategy and RPG games, reading, draw and on the free time, i am a musician too. My favorite musical genre? Jazz, rock and R&B.

EDUCATION

Udemy

UX & Design Thinking
UI com foco em UX
Design Sprints
Testes de Usabilidade
Métricas de UX e Negócios

UNIP - Univ. de São Paulo

Bachelor of Social Communication Publicity and Advertising

LANGUAGE

Portuguese Native English Advanced

TOOLS

Design & Prototype

Sketch, Invision, Figma, XD, Photoshop, Illustrator

Code

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Angular, React Native

Methodologies

Design Sprint, Double Diamond, Lean Ux, Design Thinking, Scrum

EXPERIENCE

U	d	e	n	าy
•	•	•		

UX mentor

Present

Ux mentor on the UX e Negócios course from Udemy

Freelancer

UI Designer and front-end dev.

2011- Present

Offers consulting in ux/ui designer

Prototyping screens and flow to websites and blogs;

Development responsive layout of websites using Wordpress, HTML/CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap 4.

Imersão UX Unicórnio 19

Ux/Ui designer

2019

Worked and participate on a Hackathon and UX Immersion Program, where I did the scope management, survey acquiring information for validation of hypothesis.

After this I worked with Design Sprint passing by all the steps: map, sketch, decide, prototype and test with users.

PWI

UI designer e front-end dev.

2016 - 2018

Participate in meeting with client for survey scope

Prototyping screens and flow to websites and app projects

Development layout of websites, app and softwares using HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React Native, Bootstrap 4 and other frameworks and pre-compilers like less and sass

Some of clients that i had the pleasure to work for while i am on this company: Parque Beto Carrero, Forever Living, Wet'n Wild, Diverte Cultural and Grupo Dreams

MIG

Entrepreuner

2013 - 2016

Entrepreneur on a micro agency of digital marketing.

Participate in meeting with client for survey scope and made proposals

Prototyping screens and flow to websites and development.

Top Clip

Designer clipping and communication assistant

2009 - 2013

As designer/clipping:

Design the layout of magazine and newspaper.

Supervised OCR of selected clipping and sent to Renault and General Motors

As communication assistant:

Receive the clients' briefing and organize the task of each department of company

Planned the keywords based on the client's marketing strategy

Some of clients that i had the pleasure to work for when i was on this company: Volkswagen, Renault, O Boticário